export default createAlphabet = (fire) => {
  const prompts = [
    {"prompt":"अ","correct":"a"},
    {"prompt":"आ","correct":"aa"},
    {"prompt":"ए","correct":"e"},
    {"prompt":"ई","correct":"ii"},
    {"prompt":"ऍ","correct":"ei"},
    {"prompt":"ऎ","correct":"ei"},
    {"prompt":"ऐ","correct":"ai"},
    {"prompt":"इ","correct":"i"},
    {"prompt":"ओ","correct":"o"},
    {"prompt":"ऑ","correct":"oi"},
    {"prompt":"ऒ","correct":"oii"},
    {"prompt":"ऊ","correct":"uu"},
    {"prompt":"औ","correct":"ou"},
    {"prompt":"उ","correct":"u"},
    {"prompt":"ब","correct":"B"},
    {"prompt":"भ","correct":"Bha"},
    {"prompt":"च","correct":"Ca"},
    {"prompt":"छ","correct":"Chha"},
    {"prompt":"ड","correct":"Da"},
    {"prompt":"ढ","correct":"Dha"},
    {"prompt":"फ","correct":"Fa"},
    {"prompt":"फ़","correct":"Fi"},
    {"prompt":"ग","correct":"Ga"},
    {"prompt":"घ","correct":"Gha"},
    {"prompt":"ग़","correct":"Ghi"},
    {"prompt":"ह","correct":"Ha"},
    {"prompt":"ज","correct":"Ja"},
    {"prompt":"झ","correct":"Jha"},
    {"prompt":"क","correct":"Ka"},
    {"prompt":"ख","correct":"Kha"},
    {"prompt":"ख़","correct":"Khi"},
    {"prompt":"ल","correct":"L"},
    {"prompt":"ळ","correct":"Li"},
    {"prompt":"ऌ","correct":"Li"},
    {"prompt":"ऴ","correct":"Lii"},
    {"prompt":"ॡ","correct":"Lii"},
    {"prompt":"म","correct":"Ma"},
    {"prompt":"न","correct":"Na"},
    {"prompt":"ङ","correct":"N'a"},
    {"prompt":"ञ","correct":"Nia"},
    {"prompt":"ण","correct":"Nae"},
    {"prompt":"ऩ","correct":"Ni"},
    {"prompt":"ॐ","correct":"oms"},
    {"prompt":"प","correct":"Pa"},
    {"prompt":"क़","correct":"Qi"},
    {"prompt":"र","correct":"Ra"},
    {"prompt":"ऋ","correct":"Ri"},
    {"prompt":"ॠ","correct":"Ri"},
    {"prompt":"ऱ","correct":"Ri"},
    {"prompt":"स","correct":"Sa"},
    {"prompt":"श","correct":"Sha"},
    {"prompt":"ष","correct":"Shha"},
    {"prompt":"ट","correct":"Ta"},
    {"prompt":"त","correct":"T'a"},
    {"prompt":"ठ","correct":"Tha"},
    {"prompt":"द","correct":"Tha"},
    {"prompt":"थ","correct":"T'ha"},
    {"prompt":"ध","correct":"Thha"},
    {"prompt":"ड़","correct":"ugDha"},
    {"prompt":"ढ़","correct":"ugDhha"},
    {"prompt":"व","correct":"Va"},
    {"prompt":"य","correct":"Ya"},
    {"prompt":"य़","correct":"Yi"},
    {"prompt":"ज़","correct":"Za"}
  ]
  const choices = [
    "a",
    "aa",
    "e",
    "ii",
    "ei",
    "ei",
    "ai",
    "i",
    "o",
    "oi",
    "oii",
    "uu",
    "ou",
    "u",
    "B",
    "Bha",
    "Ca",
    "Chha",
    "Da",
    "Dha",
    "Fa",
    "Fi",
    "Ga",
    "Gha",
    "Ghi",
    "Ha",
    "Ja",
    "Jha",
    "Ka",
    "Kha",
    "Khi",
    "L",
    "Li",
    "Li",
    "Lii",
    "Lii",
    "Ma",
    "Na",
    "N'a",
    "Nia",
    "Nae",
    "Ni",
    "oms",
    "Pa",
    "Qi",
    "Ra",
    "Ri",
    "Ri",
    "Ri",
    "Sa",
    "Sha",
    "Shha",
    "Ta",
    "T'a",
    "Tha",
    "Tha",
    "T'ha",
    "Thha",
    "ugDha",
    "ugDhha",
    "Va",
    "Ya",
    "Yi",
    "Za"
  ]
  const parentRef = fire.database().ref('/lessons/alphabetForBeginners');
  const choicesRef = fire.database().ref(`/lessons/alphabetForBeginners/choices`);
  const promptsRef = fire.database().ref(`/lessons/alphabetForBeginners/prompts`);
  parentRef.push({title: 'Hindi Alphabet'});
  for(let i=0 ; i <= prompts.length ; i++){
    let key = choicesRef.push(prompts[i].correct).key;
    promptsRef.push({
      prompt: prompts[i].prompt,
      key: key
    });
  }
}
